shopcartusa.com 2005-12-10

# ShopCartUSA.com - Join FREE!

**Your Privacy**  
ShopCartUSA believes that trust is an important component of the service we provide to our customers. To ensure that we earn and keep that trust, ShopCartUSA makes every effort to protect your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes the steps we take to make sure that when you use ShopCartUSA, you can focus on finding great deals in a safe, worry-free environment. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
This site contains links to other Web sites. ShopCartUSA is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites. If you have concerns about how other Web sites collect and use information about you, make sure to read that site’s own privacy policy. 

**Sharing Information**  
Unless you give explicit permission (e.g., you opt to receive e-mail from partners and third parties), ShopCartUSA has a strict policy against sharing or selling your personal information (such as your e-mail address or mailing address), except when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or to protect the rights, safety or property of ShopCartUSA, our users, or others.

**Cookies**   
ShopCartUSA uses "cookies" to automatically recognize returning users. A cookie is a small file on your hard drive that allows us to display your previously defined search criteria and notification preferences whenever you visit our site. You can block cookies by changing the settings on your browser (contact your ISP for help), but doing so may prevent us from delivering certain services to you (e.g., saved searches). 

**User Information**  
The use of certain ShopCartUSA features requires that you supply personal information like your name and e-mail address. At your direction, we may use this information to send you our e-mail newsletter. This information may also be used to contact you when necessary. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time (see the “Choice/Opt-Out” section below). 

**Choice/Opt-Out of ShopCartUSA E-mail Communications**  
At any time, you have the ability to opt-out of receiving communications from ShopCartUSA and our partners. To unsubscribe from the ShopCartUSA e-mail newsletter, contact customersupport@ShopCartUSA.com and let us know that you would like to discontinue this service. 

**Special Relationships**  
ShopCartUSA enters into special relationships to offer a broader array of services to our users. On occasions when we partner with another service to bring you more comparison-shopping functionality, such as with our automobile category, we do not host these pages on our own servers. In these instances, information may be collected but it is being collected by the partner and not by ShopCartUSA. ShopCartUSA may receive information from these partners, only when it is clearly stated. Unless you give explicit permission, ShopCartUSA has a strict policy against sharing or selling your personal information and only aggregated (and not individual) data is used by ShopCartUSA. 

**IP Address Logging**  
ShopCartUSA logs IP addresses (your unique Internet address) for system administration purposes. IP addresses are logged to give us an idea of which parts of our site users are visiting so that we can update and improve the services we offer to you. We do not link IP addresses to any information that could personally identify you. This means that the path of your ShopCartUSA session will be tracked, but you will remain anonymous. 

**Tell a Friend**  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. ShopCartUSA collects the email address of your friend for the sole purpose of automatically sending the friend an email inviting them to visit the site and does not store this information. 

**Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

**Security**  
Using the latest security measures and technologies, we keep a tight watch on the information you give to ShopCartUSA to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the data under our control.

**Notification of Changes**  
Should ShopCartUSA decide to change our policy concerning the use of your personal information, we will post all changes in this privacy policy 30 days prior to the date the change goes into effect. If you would like to receive e-mail notification of any such changes, please contact us at customersupport@ShopCartUSA.com requesting the same. 

**Contacting Us**

> If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact:
> 
> **ShopCartUSA Web Site Coordinator**  
>  ShopCartUSA.com, Inc.  
>  2744 Atlantic Avenue  
>  Brooklyn, NY 11207
